Sara Khan

4 Waterside Road Southall Middlesex UB2 4RA

Mobile: 07960688907

Email: sarak3098@gmail.com

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am very keen on developing my current skills and abilities. I am reliable, very punctual with excellent telephone manners. I am capable of using Microsoft Office programs including word and excel. I am also able to use content creation applications such as Canva. I have very good communication skills which enables me to interact well with others. After volunteering for several years I feel I am interested in social media.

WORK HISTORY

July 2022 to November 2022

Social Media Volunteer

Ealing 135

Creating posters for local playgroups

December 2021 to Present

Social Media Volunteer

The Safe Foundation
Creating content using Canva for Instagram
Creating Content using Canva for Facebook
Creating blogs
Design & researching mailshots
Sharing content via social media platforms
Regularly gathering social media analytics
Creating techniques giving feedback to the organisation

December 2021 to June 2022

Social Media Volunteer

Ealing Nub News

Uploading content to Instagram

Uploading content to Facebook

Gathering other news / stories to upload on Social Media

April 2017 to January 2019

Volunteer Admin worker

Havelock Family Centre

Answering telephone calls
Scanning documentation
Filing
Faxing
Inputting client details on to the database
Ensuring membership list up to date
Making sure clients are seen to the relevant advisors
Assisting the manager when required

Sara Khan

4 Waterside Road Southall Middlesex UB2 4RA Mobile: 07960688907 Email: sarak3098@gmail.com

June 2016 to February 2017

Volunteer Admin worker

P.E.S.T.S - Special Needs - Play & support group

Inputting on to the database staff records of name, addresses, attendance, sickness

Fundraising

Encourage ways to fundraise such as donation

Campaign to schools and small businesses

Creating induction fundraising document

Advertising volunteers

Using Microsoft publisher to create electronic newsletter

Creating staff results monitoring form

Setting up website

Safeguarding course

March 2008 to 2014

Volunteer Assistant

Ealing Mencap Gateway Wednesday Club, Perivale

A weekly youth club for teenagers with disabilities

Assist club members who have disabilities in various activities such as arts and crafts, cooking sessions and sports activities

Provide support to Club Leader in the preparation of Wednesday Club

Assist in workshops

June 2007 to July 2012

Volunteer Receptionist/ Administrator

TASHA Foundation, Hanwell

A charitable organisation dealing with alcohol and drug misuse

Using database to contact clients and re-schedule appointments

Answering telephone calls and taking messages

Drafting letters

Producing and typing documents

Distribute incoming and outgoing mail

Filing, Faxing, Photocopying, Franking

June 2010 to December 2010

Learning and Development Assistant

Ealing Council Perceval House People & Organisational Development Team

Assisting with research with Ealing Council or London Boroughs regarding learning development Helping create databases of both previous and potential customers to boost potential of LearnCenter

Carry out presentations to council departments on learning and development

Inputting data on spreadsheets

Help set up e-learning roadshows

Assisting colleagues in Microsoft office tasks

March 2005

Office Assistant

Havelock Family Centre, Southall

A voluntary organisation that provides services for children and families

Maintaining the guest signing in book

Maintaining register book for child contact

Sara Khan

4 Waterside Road Southall Middlesex UB2 4RA

Mobile: 07960688907

Email: sarak3098@gmail.com

TRAINING

September 2010 to March 2011 West Thames College ITQ Level 2 (ECDL Extra) tests. September 2008 to May 2009

Adult Numeracy

TBG Learning, Southall

EDI Level 1

EDUCATION

November 2007 to July 2008

Entry to employment

TBG Learning, Southall

Literacy skills

Numeracy skills

Soft skills working with people in work experience

Interview techniques

September 2006 to May 2007

Cranford Community College

BTEC First Diploma in Business - Grade Merit

GNVQ Leisure & Tourism Grade Pass

September 2001 to June 2006

Featherstone High School, Southall

9 GCSE passed at D - F

REFERENCES

Angela Bettany	Alan J Eastwood
Operations Director	45 Hadcroft Grange
The SAFE Foundation	Stourbridge
Railway Gardens	West Midlands
Adeline St,	DY9 7EP
Splott,	Alaneastwood@hotmail.com
Cardiff	
CF24 2BH	
angiesafe101@gmail.com	